İletişim Bilgileri

tb-pala@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hüseyin-pala-89962b21b (LinkedIn)

En Önemli Yetenekler

Japonca

Almanca

Unity

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Turkish (Native or Bilingual)
Germany (Elementary)

Certifications

Google Flutter İle Mobil Uygulama Geliştiriciliği

Advanced java programming

Hüseyin Pala

Mobile Application Development/Software engineer istanbul, Türkiye

Özet

I took my first step in programming by learning the java programming language in 2019 and then tried to improve myself in programming languages such as android studio, flutter, html/css/js, MsSQL, PostgreSQL, Firebase, and Unity. Currently, mobile application development with flutter and java back-end side. I am trying to improve myself by writing my codes.

I am a 3rd-year Computer Engineering student and I am open and ready to improve myself and add new things to my life.

Along with the software, I have been dealing with bodybuilding for about 4 years.

I can speak, understand and read English at the B2 level.

Deneyim

Kütahya Dumlupınar Üniversitesi Student Eylül 2019 - Present (3 yıl 7 ay) Kütahya, Türkiye

Magis Technology Mobile Application Developer Temmuz 2022 - Ağustos 2022 (2 ay) İstanbul, Türkiye

I have a working history of 5 weeks as a mobile application developer.

Eğitim

Kütahya Dumlupınar Üniversitesi Lisans Derecesi, Bilgisayar Mühendisliği · (Eylül 2020 - Haziran 2024)

Patika.dev

Bootcamp Acceleration Program -2022 · (Kasım 2022 - Kasım 2023)

Patika.dev